Subindex build by Linnet
http://linnet.126.com  http://blog.csdn.net/redbirdli
火鸟字幕合并器SubindexV0.5
Created time 10.04.04 11:54:36
Blue velvet
Whoa- Whoa
她穿着蓝丝绒
She wore blue velvet
Whoa- Whoa
蓝得比夜晚还要蓝
Bluer than velvet was the night
Whoa- Whoa- Whoa
柔软得比星星的光还要柔软
Softer than satin was the light
From the stars
她穿着蓝丝绒
She wore blue velvet
蓝得比她的双眼还要蓝
Whoa- Whoa
Bluer than velvet were her eyes
Whoa- Whoa- Whoa
温暖得比她的柔情还要温暖
Warmer than May her tender sighs
我们的爱
Love was ours
我是如此珍惜那份爱
Ours a love I held tightly
对她愈来愈迷恋
Feeling the rapture grow
像是火焰发出光芒
Like a flame burning brightly
但是当她离去…
But when she left
蓝丝绒的光芒也消失
Gone was the glow of blue velvet
Whoa- Whoa
只有在我心中她们常在
But in my heart there'll always be
Whoa- Whoa- Whoa
珍贵地保有这份回忆
Precious and warm a memory
年复一年…
Through the years...
砍伐，砍伐，砍伐
Logs, logs, logs
丛林中如此喧嚣
Glamour in the pines
伐木镇
Lumberton
美国
USA
今天的伐木镇又是阳光明媚的一天
It's a sunny, woodsy day in Lumberton, so get those chain saws out.
大伙又可以带着电锯出门砍伐了
这里是WOOD电台…
This is the mighty W-O-O-D, the musical voice of Lumberton.
伐木镇的音乐之声
大树倒下的声音响起时…
At the sound of the falling tree...
现在是九点三十分
it's 9.30!
茂盛的丛林中还有众多的树木等着被砍倒
There's a whole lotta wood Waitin' out there, so let's get goin'.
让我们继续努力吧
博蒙特先生
Mr Beaumont?
你儿子杰弗里来看你了
Your son Jeffrey's here to see you.
嗨，爸爸
Hey, Dad.
（ 伐木镇警察局 ）
你好，请问威廉斯探长还在吗？
Do you have a Detective Williams still working here?
在，就在楼上221室
Yes, he's up in room 221.
穿过那扇门上楼就是
- Right up the stairs, through that door. - Thanks.
谢谢
威廉斯探长？
Detective Williams?
什么事？
Yes?
我叫杰弗里博蒙特，就住在你家附近
My name is Jeffrey Beaumont. I live near you. I believe you know my father Tom?
我想你该认识我父亲
汤姆博蒙特，博蒙特五金店的老板
- Beaumont's Hardware Store? - Sure I do. I hear he's in the hospital.
当然认识，听说他进了医院
身体怎样了？
- How's he doing? - Well, he's OK, I guess. I hope.
我想该是没事了，希望如此吧
他们还在给他做检查，因此我就休学回家了
They're doing tests. I was at the hospital this morning
我今早看完他回来
and, coming home through the field behind Vista,
在穿过邻居家后面荒地的时候
我发现了一只耳朵
I... found an ear.
什么？是人耳吗？
You did? A human ear?
我觉得该拿来给你看看
Yeah. I thought I should bring it to you.
你做得很对，让我来瞧瞧
Yeah, that's right. Let's take a look at it.
确实是人耳
Yes, that's a human ear, all right.
先把这拿到验尸官那儿去
Let's see what the coroner makes of it.
然后你再带我去现场
Then I want you to show me exactly where you found it.
好
All right.
我们会去查陈尸房的记录
We'll check the morgue records, but I don't recall anything minus an ear.
可我不记得有什么尸体少了耳朵
耳朵的主人可能还活着
The person may very well still be alive somewhere.
从这耳朵能知道它主人的身份吗？
What can you tell about the person from the ear?
得先做大量的化验…
Once the tests are done, quite a lot.
鉴别性别、血型，还要看是否死后才割下来的
Sex, blood type, whether the ear came off a dead person.
此外…这看来…像是被剪刀剪下来的
Also, it looks like the ear was cut off with scissors.
我想出去走走
- I'm goin' out for a while. - Do you want the car?
想要用车？
- No, I'm just gonna walk around. - All right.
不，只是随便走走　　　好吧
你不会去林肯街吧？
You're not going down by Lincoln, are you?
不，我就在附近走走
No, just around the neighbourhood. Don't worry.
别担心
好吧，亲爱的
OK, honey.
你好，我是杰弗里博蒙特
Hello. My name is Jeffrey Beaumont. Is Detective Williams here?
威廉斯探长在吗？
- Oh, yes. Yes, Jeffrey, come on in. - Thanks.
他在，进来吧，杰弗里
多谢
杰弗里，你找到的东西很有意思
Well, Jeffrey, you found something very interesting.
非常有意思
Very interesting. I know you must be curious to know more.
我明白你定想多了解些情况
但恐怕我得请你严守秘密
But I have to ask you not only not to tell anybody about your find,
而且也别再插手这案件了
but also not to ask more about the case.
等到水落石出的那天
One day when it's all sewed up,
我一定会告诉你全部细节
I'll let you know all the details.
可是现在还不行
Right now, though, I can't.
我明白
I understand. I'm just real curious, like you said.
我只不过是很好奇罢了
我年轻的时候也和你一样
I was the same way myself when I was your age.
所以后来才做了这行
- That's what got me into this business. - Must be great.
感觉一定很棒
但也很可怕
It's horrible, too.
我很抱歉，杰弗里
I'm sorry, Jeffrey. That's the way it has to be.
事情只能是这样了
我想你明白我的苦衷
Anyway, I know you do understand.
是的
Sure.
谢谢你帮我父亲的忙
- Thanks for the card for Dad. - You're welcome. Nice to meet you.
不用客气
能认识你真不错，杰弗里
You, too.
我也是
请代我向桑蒂问好　　　好
- Say hello to Sandy for me. - We will.
晚安，杰弗里
- Good night, Jeffrey. - Good night.
晚安，威廉斯探长
耳朵是你找到的？
Are you the one that found the ear?
你怎么知道的？
How did you know?
我就是知道
I just know, that's all.
我在学校见过你
- I remember you from Central. - Are you a senior?
是吗？你读四年级？　　对
最近学校怎么样？
Yup.
- How is Central these days? - Terrible.
很糟糕，无聊的很
- I don't know... Boring. - What else is new!
没新鲜的事了，对吗？
是的，你最近如何？
So what are you doin' now?
我暂时休学，父亲住院了
I'm home from school. My father's in the hospital.
太可惜了
- That's too bad. - Yeah.
是啊，你怎么知道耳朵的事情？
What do you know about the ear?
我爸不是已经叫你少管了吗？
- Didn't Dad say not to talk about it? - Yeah, but you brought it up.
对，可是你先说起的
你知道些什么吗？
You know anything?
知道得不多，零零碎碎的
I don't know much but bits and pieces. I hear things.
我对此有些耳闻
Yeah?
我房间的楼下就是父亲的书房
- My room is above my father's office so... - Above your father's office?
在他书房的上面？
所以我就听到了点关于耳朵的事
- So I heard a few things about the ear. - Uh-huh. And?
是什么？
Well... there are a couple of cases I get mixed up on.
还有些案子好像也与此有关
那有一个女歌手
But one name that keeps coming up is this woman singer.
她就在你家附近租了公寓
She lives in an apartment real close to your house.
也靠近那片荒地
Close to the field where you found the ear.
这世界无奇不有，不是吗？
It's a strange world, isn't it?
是啊
- Yeah. - Where is this apartment?
知道那女人的家在哪吗？
It's really close by. That's what's so creepy.
离这儿很近，那街区很乱
他们已经监视她好几个月
They had her under surveillance,
我也不知道他们有何收获
'cept I don't know what they found out cos she's not my dad's case. So...
因为那案子不归我爸管
我想你还不急着回家吧
I guess you gotta get back home pretty soon, huh?
不急，有什么事？
Not really. Why?
好吧…
Well...
你想去见见那屋子
- You... wanna see the building. - Yeah.
没错　　　来吧，我带你去
- Come on, I'll show you. - OK.
嗨，宝贝
Hey, baby. Hey, babe.
就是那栋
That's her building right there.
她住在七楼
She lives on the seventh floor.
走吧
Come on.
（ 林肯街 ）
那你如今在家都做些什么？
So... what are you gonna do now that you're home?
帮着打理家里的五金店
Help out at my father's hardware store.
有自由时间，还算不错
They're giving me my own hours, which is nice.
我曾和住这家的孩子很熟
I used to know a kid that lived there.
他是我见过说话最结巴的家伙
Had the biggest tongue in the world.
后来他怎么样了？
What happened to him?
不知道，搬走了吧
I don't know. He moved away.
所有的老朋友都走光了
All my old friends are gone.
知道我们怎么学鸡走吗？
- You know the chicken walk? - What's that?
怎么样？
那可真有趣
That's kind of interesting.
该休息啦
Coffee time.
是艾德兄弟啊，那些防护服呢？
Hey, Double Ed, where are the overalls?
在架子的底部
They're on the bottom shelf, rolled up, where they've always been.
就在平时摆放的地方
来，艾德，猜猜是几个手指？
Hey, Ed, how many fingers?
四个
Four.
我总搞不明白你是怎么办到的
I still don't know how you do that.
需要我帮忙喷杀虫水吗？
Now listen. You sure you don't need me or this rig for a while?
除非你想要应付那些虫子，杰弗里…
If you wanna spray for bugs, Jeffrey, it causes us no pain.
我们是无所谓的
没问题
Okey-dokey, Double Ed.
见到你回来真好　　　是啊
- Oh, it's so good to have you back. - Yeah, sure.
你是饿了？渴了？或者两者皆是
You hungry or thirsty, or both?
我不知道
- I don't know. - I'd like to talk to you about somethin'.
我想要和你谈谈
稍等
Wait just a minute.
你们可千万别告诉麦克
Listen. Don't you guys dare say anything to Mike.
好的　　　事情不是你们想的那样
- Sure. - It's not what you think, OK?
你们保证？好的
- Promise? - Whatever you say.
我可不想惹什么麻烦
- I don't wanna cause trouble. - I'm here, aren't I?
我这不是来了吧
- He is nice-lookin'. - Yeah.
他真英俊
去过亚琳餐厅吗？
You ever been to Arlene's?
当然
Of course.
你还没说出你的来意
Now are you gonna tell me why we're here?
生命中有很多获得磨练，增长阅历的机会
There are opportunities in life for gaining knowledge and experience.
有时候也需要冒险
Sometimes it's necessary to take a risk.
我在想的是…
I'll bet someone could learn a lot by getting into that woman's apartment.
若是能潜入那女人的公寓
收获肯定不小
偷偷溜进去，藏好，再观察
You know, sneak in, hide, and observe.
溜进她的住处？对
- Sneak into her apartment? - Yeah.
你这是疯了吗？
Are you crazy?
杰弗里，她也许和凶杀案有关
Jeffrey, she's possibly involved in murder. This is givin' me the creeps.
这想法太可怕了
Now just settle down. I have a plan which I think will work.
先安心听我说
我有个可行的计划
虽然不怎么费事
There's very little for you to do, but I do need your help.
但却需要你帮忙
你连听听都不愿意吗？
Don't you even wanna hear the plan?
你愿意说就说
Tell me any plan you want, but it's not going any further than this diner.
但这就和这顿午餐一样，毫无意义
桑蒂
Sandy,
别用这种态度嘛
don't take that attitude.
好了
All right. The first thing I need is to get into her apartment
首先我要进入她的公寓…
打开扇窗子，以便以后进去
- And open a window to crawl into later. - How are you gonna do that?
怎么进去？
Right out in the car I happen to have some old overalls and a bug-spraying rig.
在外面的车上
我有些旧防护服及杀虫剂
我去她公寓假装来喷杀虫剂
I will go to her apartment as a pest-control man. I will spray her apartment.
几分钟后你去敲门吸引她的注意
You knock on the door, draw her attention away from me, and I'll jimmy a window.
我就趁机撬开窗子
那她来应门的时候我该说什么？
- And what do I say to her at the door? - You will be a Jehovah's witness.
你就装成是传教的
我为你准备了些《觉醒》之类的杂志
I have some Awake!  magazines for you.
不需要太多时间，几分钟而已
I don't need very much time, just a few seconds. Whaddaya think?
你看如何？
不知道
I don't know.
听起来像是个漂亮的白日梦
I mean, it sounds like a good daydream, but... actually doing it's too weird.
但实在是太怪异了
这么做太危险
- It's too dangerous. - Sandy, let's just try the first part.
桑蒂，先试试看吧
没有人会怀疑我们
No one will suspect us.
他们不会想到有人会那么疯狂
No one would think two people like us would be crazy enough to do this.
说的有理
You have a point there.
（ 深河公寓 ）
我进门后，过三分钟你再来
Give me at least three minutes.
我可以拖延下时间
I can stall if it's more, but I need time to find a good window. All right?
但得给我时间找合适的窗子
好吧
All right.
走
Let's go.
我先上去了
Here I go.
等等，她叫什么名字来着？
Wait a minute. What's her name?
天啊，杰弗里
Oh, brother, Jeffrey.
桃乐茜华伦，七楼
Dorothy Vallens, seventh floor.
查她信箱可以知道房间号
Look on her mailbox for the number, bright boy.
多谢
Thanks.
桃乐茜华伦，七楼
Dorothy Vallens, seventh floor.
OK. Good luck.
祝你好运
Good luck yourself.
还是祝你自己吧
三分钟后再来，别太早了
Three minutes. No sooner.
（ 电梯已坏，请用楼梯 ）
请问有什么事？
Yes? What is it?
公司派我来杀虫
Pest control. I gotta do your apartment.
杀虫剂的味道很难闻
- That stuff stinks. - This is new stuff. There's no smell.
这是新型药剂，无味的
那就好
Good.
只需在厨房喷点就可以了
Just need to do the kitchen.
来的人还真多
Grand Central Station.
只不过是个杀虫的
It's only the bug man.
那样就差不多了
- That should do it. - Yeah?
你没事吧？你那儿出了什么问题？
- Are you all right? - Yeah. What happened?
我刚要来敲门，却被那人抢先一步
I was about to go to the door when that guy did it for me.
没出事吧？
- Was it all right? - Yes and no. Did you recognise him?
很难说，你认得那个人吗？
我只看到他背面
I only saw his back. I think he went out a door at the end of the hall.
他好像是从另外的门离开的
我也没能怎么仔细打量他
I didn't get a good look at him either, but he sure looked at me.
可他把我看了个仔仔细细
I didn't have time to get a window, but I found these keys. Nifty, huh?
没时间去搞开窗子，但我找到了些钥匙
干得很漂亮吧
Yeah, if they open the door.
得能开得了门再说
对
Yeah.
那接下来该去干什么？
So, what's next?
你还想玩下去吗？
- Are you game for more? - I owe you one since I goofed this one up.
我把这事搞砸了，算我欠你的
你没搞砸什么
You didn't goof it up. But... you still owe me one.
但还是欠我一次
今晚上溜进去？
I'm gonna try and sneak in tonight.
今晚是周末，有约会吗？
It's Friday. Do you have a date?
是的，我有
Yeah. I do.
好吧，没戏唱了
Well, that does that.
你不会真想去干吧？
- You really wanna do this, don't you? - I don't want you to get involved.
我不想连累你
我要去，若是出了事
I do, but if something went wrong...
如你所说，这可能牵扯到凶杀案
Like you said, they may be involved in murder.
那我就和麦克说我病了
OK. I'll tell Mike I'm sick.
丑话说在前面
Just so the record is kept straight, though,
我爱麦克
I love Mike.
你要我怎么做？
What do you want me to do?
我们先去吃顿丰盛的晚餐
First we'll have a really nice dinner. Try to find out where Dorothy Vallens sings.
再打听桃乐茜华伦在哪唱歌
我知道，是在七区的史洛俱乐部
I already know. The Slow Club on Route 7.
太好了，我八点来接你？
Great. I'll pick you up about eight?
不用接我了，否则我爸会起疑心
Don't pick me up. My dad might think it's strange.
我会走路去你家
I'll walk over to your house. I'll be there at eight o'clock. OK?
八点到好吗？
趁现在没人你快走吧
You better get out before someone sees us.
晚上见
See ya!
（ 史洛俱乐部 ）
对了
Wait. Here's to an interesting experience, huh?
为这有趣的体验干杯
干杯
I'll drink to that.
我很喜欢喜力啤酒，你喜欢吗？
Man, I like Heineken! You like Heineken?
之前从未尝过
- I never really had Heineken before. - You never had Heineken before?
你没喝过喜力啤酒？
我父亲喜欢喝巴德牌
My dad drinks Bud.
那可是啤酒之王
- King of beers. - Ladies and gentlemen,
女士们先生们
接下来表演的是蓝夜之后…
the Blue Lady, Miss Dorothy Vallens.
桃乐茜华伦小姐
她
She
穿着
Wore
蓝丝绒
Blue velvet
蓝的比夜晚还要蓝
Bluer than velvet was the night
柔软得比星星的光还要柔软
Softer than satin was the light
From the stars
她穿着蓝丝绒
She wore blue velvet
蓝得比她双眼还要蓝
Bluer than velvet were her eyes
那影子
Shadows
如此的蓝
Fall so blue
就如那孤寂的
As lonely as a blue
蓝色
Blue
星星
Star
杰弗里，你不该这么做
- Jeffrey, you shouldn't do this. - Why not?
为什么？
因为这太疯狂…
Cos it's crazy... and dangerous.
又危险
我真不该告诉你的
- My God, I should have never told you. - I'll be all right.
不会有事的
I don't think you should stay. I think you should go home. Can you drive this car?
我想你还是先回家吧
能开这车吗？
能，但是…
- Yeah, but I... - Leave it in front of your house, OK?
就把它停在你家门口，我会去拿的
好吧
OK.
明天会告诉你事情经过
I'll see ya tomorrow and I'll tell ya how it went.
明天我不能来见你
I don't wanna see you tomorrow.
麦克会来我家
- Mike's coming over. - OK. Can I call you?
那我能给你电话吗？
可以
OK, yeah, call.
希望你进得去还出得来
I hope you sneak out OK.
我会在这儿等到她回来
- I'm gonna wait here until she comes. - Sandy...
她来了我就按四下喇叭
I'm gonna honk four times.
节奏就是：一，二，三，四
I'll go one, two, three, four, and then you'll hear it
那样你就知道她上来了
- And you'll know she's on her way up. - OK.
真搞不懂你是大侦探还是变态
I don't know if you're a detective or a pervert.
我自己也想搞明白，走着瞧吧
Well, that's for me to know and you to find out.
再见
See ya.
Bye.
喝太多啤酒了
Heineken.
希望你平安无事，杰弗里
I hope you're OK, Jeffrey.
谢谢你，吉米，明天见
Thank you, Jimmy. See you tomorrow. Good night.
晚安
喂？是的，先生
Hello? Yes, sir. Frank? Frank, let me talk to him.
弗兰克？弗兰克，让我和他说说话
求求你了，弗兰克
Please, Frank... sir.
我喜欢唱“蓝丝绒”
I like to sing "Blue Velvet".
唐尼，没事的，别担心
Don... Don, it's all right, don't worry. Don! Don, can you hear me?
唐尼，听到我说话吗？
小唐尼没事吧？
Is little Donny all right?
他和你在一起吗？
Is he there with you?
唐尼？
Don?
你是说牧场路？
You mean Meadow Lane? Frank! Frank, what's the matter with him?
弗兰克，他怎么了？
我知道，我会乖乖的
I know. I'll be sweet.
妈妈爱你
Mommy loves you.
好的，弗兰克，先生
OK, Frank... sir.
快给我出来！出来！
Get out of there! Get out!
把手举起来！把手放在头上！快！
Put your hands up! On your head! Do it!
跪下来！
Get on your knees! Do it!
你来这儿干什么？
What are you doing?
你是谁？叫什么名字？
- Who are you? What's your name? - Jeffrey.
杰弗里
- Jeffrey what? - Jeffrey nothing.
姓什么？
就是杰弗里
把你的钱包给我
Give me your wallet. Give me your wallet!
“杰弗里博蒙特”
Jeffrey Beaumont. What are you doing in my apartment, Jeffrey Beaumont?
你闯进我家干什么，杰弗里博蒙特？
我想来看你
- I wanted to see you. - Are you kidding?
开什么玩笑？
谁派你来的？没人派我来
- Who sent you here? - Nobody.
我好像见过你
- I've seen you before. - I sprayed your apartment.
我来你家里喷杀虫水，然后拿走了你的钥匙
I took your key. I didn't mean to do anything except see you.
我什么也不想做，只想看看你而已
那你今晚看到了什么？
What did you see, tonight?
说！
- Tell me! - I saw you come in, talk on the phone...
我看见你进来然后接电话
接下来呢？
- And then? - You got undressed.
你脱掉了衣服
你喜欢摸进女生的家里
Do you sneak in girls' apartments to see them get undressed?
偷看她们换衣服吗？
不，以前从未这样
No, never before this.
脱衣服，让我看
- Get undressed. I want to see you. - Look, I'm sorry. Just let me leave.
对不起，放我走吧
No way! I want to see you! Get undressed!
不行！我要看你脱衣服
站起来
Stand up.
过来
Come closer.
再近些
Closer.
你想要做什么？
What do you want?
我不知道
I don't know.
别动
Don't move. Don't look at me.
也别看我
你喜欢这样吗？是的
- Do you like that? - Yes.
别碰我！不然我杀了你！
Don't touch me! Or I'll kill you!
你喜欢我这样子说话吗？
Do you like talk like that?
不
No.
过去沙发那边
Get over there on that couch.
躺下
Lie down.
闭上嘴，别出声
Shut up! Don't say anything. Hide in the closet.
快回衣柜里去
Don't say anything, or I'll kill you. I mean it.
不许出声，不然我杀了你
我不开玩笑
你好，宝贝
- Hello, baby. - Shut up!
住嘴！叫我爸爸！
It's Daddy, you shithead! Where's my bourbon?
我的酒呢？
你他妈怎么那么没记性？
Can't you fuckin' remember anything?
现在天黑了
Now it's dark.
把腿分开
Spread your legs.
再开点
Wider.
给我看
Now show it to me.
不许看着老子
Don't you fuckin' look at me.
妈妈
Mommy...
Mommy! Mommy!
- Mommy... - Mommy loves you, Frank.
妈妈爱你
宝宝想要做爱
Baby wants to fuck!
快让我干！你这婊子！
All right, get ready to fuck! You fucker's fucker! You fucker!
婊子！
他妈不许看着老子！
Don't you fuckin' look at me!
好
宝宝想要蓝丝绒
Baby wants blue velvet.
妈妈，妈妈
不许看老子！
Don't you fuckin' look at me! Don't you fuckin' look at me!
不许看我
Look at me. Daddy's coming home.
爸爸回家了
Daddy's comin' home.
你他妈不许看老子！
Don't you fuckin' look at me!
爸爸回家了
Daddy's comin' home.
爸爸回家了！
Mommy! Mommy!
你他妈不许看老子！
Don't you fuckin' look at me!
现在天黑了
Now it's dark.
你得活下去，宝贝
You stay alive, baby.
这是为了梵高
Do it for Van Gogh.
为何不躺下来？
Why don't you lie down?
来，我来帮你
Come on, I'll help you.
我不要盖
I don't like that.
你想要什么？
What do you want?
什么也不要
Nothing.
你没事吗？
Are you all right?
没事
Yeah, I'm all right.
I'm all right.
那我走了
I'll go, then.
唐尼，唐尼
Don?
不　　　唐尼，过来抱住我
- Oh, Don! - No...
Oh, Don, hold me. Hold me.
抱住我，我好怕
I'm scared. I'm scared.
我好害怕
I'm scared!
没事了
It's OK. It's OK.
Don? Don?
你回来了
Are you back?
喜欢我吗？
Do you like me?
你喜欢我吗？　　是的
- Do you like me? - Yes.
喜欢我这样摸你吗？
Do you like the way I feel?
喜欢
Yes.
要看我的乳房吗？
See my breast?
你可以摸摸
You can feel it.
我的乳头越来越硬了
My nipple is getting hard.
你可以去碰碰
You can touch it.
你可以去摸那里
You can feel it.
喜欢这种感觉吗？
Do you like the way I feel?
喜欢
Yes.
来吧
Feel me.
打我　　　不行
Hit me.
桃乐茜，不，别这样
- Dorothy, no. Stop it. - Hit me.
来打我！
Hit me.
打我
打我啊！
Hit me!
我要走了
I'm leaving now.
唐尼
Torned.
救救我
Help me.
天，是那顶帽子
Oh, my God. That hat.
她结过婚了
She's married.
"Don."
救救我
Help me.
杰弗里
现在天黑了
Now it's dark.
打我
Hit me. Hit me.
Man, oh man.
桑蒂，你说话方便吗？
- Sandy, can ya talk? - Mike's here.
麦克在我这儿
Oh. I guess I'll talk to you later, then.
那我晚点再给你电话
事情进行的如何？
- Well, how'd it go? - It went OK. I'll tell you about it.
很顺利，待会再和你说
8点我来接你
I'll pick you up at eight.
新斧头…48721
New axe, 48721.
22.95美元
Twenty-two...
ninety-five.
那到时见　　　好极了
- I'll see ya then. - OK, great.
再见　　　再见
- Bye-bye. - Bye.
怎么了？
Well?
你不是要告诉我吗？
Aren't you gonna tell me about it?
好吧
OK.
这世界真是无奇不有，桑蒂
It's a strange world, Sandy.
桃乐茜华伦早就嫁给了叫唐尼的人
Dorothy Vallens is married, to a man named Don.
他们还有个小孩
They have a son.
我想她丈夫和小孩
I think the son and the husband have been kidnapped by a man named Frank.
该是被个叫弗兰克的所绑架
弗兰克籍此来威胁桃乐茜
Frank has done this to force Dorothy to do things for him.
以强迫她为他做事
我认为她想要寻死
I think she wants to die.
所以弗兰克砍掉他丈夫的耳朵
I think Frank cut the ear I found off her husband
做警告以让她活下去
as a warning for her to stay alive.
弗兰克是个…
Frank is...
是个极度危险的人物
a very dangerous man.
我的天
My God.
你要把这告诉我父亲吗？
- Shouldn't you tell my father? - No. I can't do that.
我不打算这么做
我还没任何证据
I can't prove any of this. I found out my information illegally.
这么做并不合法
而且会被牵涉进很多麻烦事
You could get into a lot of trouble.
昨晚上你看见许多事
You saw all that in one night?
这世界真是无奇不有
It is a strange world.
为何会有弗兰克那样的人？
Why are there people like Frank?
为何这世界上有那么多的麻烦？
Why is there so much trouble in this world?
我就是不明白
I don't know.
我做了个梦
I had a dream.
就在遇到你的那晚做的
In fact, it was the night I met you.
在那梦中，是我们的世界
In the dream, there was our world,
而那世界是黑暗的
and the world was dark because there weren't any robins.
因为那儿没有知更鸟
知更鸟就象征着爱
And the robins represented love.
很久很久…
And for the longest time there was just this darkness.
那儿一直漆黑一片
然后忽然间
And all of a sudden
成千上万的知更鸟被放出
thousands of robins were set free.
它们飞向大地
And they flew down and brought this blinding light of love.
带来了眩目的爱之光芒
在那儿爱就是…
And it seemed like that love
唯一能改变一切的力量
would be the only thing that would make any difference,
and it did.
所以我想那代表着
So I guess it means...
我们总会迎来光明的一天
there is trouble till the robins come.
你是个好女孩
You're a neat girl.
你也是
So are you.
我是说，你是个好男孩
I mean... you're a neat guy.
我们还是快走吧
I guess we better go.
我也这么想
Yeah. I guess so.
我能进来吗？
Hi. May I come in?
当然
Yes.
快进来吧
Hurry, though.
你还好吧？
Are you all right?
不好
No, I'm not.
你来这儿干什么？
Why are you here?
你想要什么？
What do you want?
我…
今晚我在衣柜里找了你整夜
I looked for you in my closet tonight.
我明白这很疯狂
It's crazy, I know. I don't know where you come from, but...
我不知道你从哪儿来
可我喜欢你
I like you.
这并不疯狂
It's not crazy. I like you too.
我也喜欢你
我想像昨晚那样
I liked being with you last night.
相同的地点
Same here.
请陪着我
Please be with me. Be with me, please.
跟我在一起
就如同
Like a flame burning brightly
火焰发出光芒
但是当她离去
But when she left
蓝丝绒的光芒也消失
Gone was the glow
Of
蓝丝绒的光芒也消失
Blue velvet
只有在我心中
But in my heart there'll always be
她们常在
珍惜地保有这份回忆
Precious and warm a memory
年复一年…
Through the years
我仍然能看到
And I still can see
蓝丝绒
Blue velvet
透过我的眼泪
Through my tears
USA
砍伐，砍伐，砍伐，伐木镇，美国
Logs, logs, logs. Lumberton, USA.
大树倒下的声音响起时
At the sound of the falling tree...
现在已是1点30分，这里是伐木镇地方电台
it's 1.30.
This is the mighty voice of Lumberton,
那里的人知道…有多少木材被砍伐
the town where people really know how much wood a woodchuck chucks.
...seven, eight, nine,
10, 1 1, 1 2,
1 3, 1 4, 1 5,
16, 1 7, 18, 1 9, 20...
快走
Keep going.
桑蒂
Sandy.
太棒了
Oh, great.
你迟到了
- You're late. - I'm sorry.
我很抱歉
- What am I gonna do now? - You wanna go talk to him?
我现在该怎么办？
需要和他谈谈吗？
Yeah, but... I don't think it's gonna do much good.
随便，不过我不觉得会有效
走吧，稍后我会和他解释
Let's just go. I'll try to talk to him later.
注意墙上的钟了吗？
See that clock on the wall?
Yeah.
接下来的五分钟里
Five minutes from now, you're not gonna believe what I've told you.
你绝对不敢相信我告诉你的话
首先…
Number one.
今天我带照相机去了弗兰克的公寓
Today I staked out Frank's place With a camera.
结果还发现有个人与此有关部门
There's another man involved in all this. I call him the Yellow Man.
我管他叫“黄人”
就是那天你在桃乐茜家门口见到的那个
You saw his back the other day at Dorothy's apartment.
我看见黄人和弗兰克进了住处
Today I saw the Yellow Man go into Frank's building, laughing with Frank.
两人有说有笑的
问题是那意味着什么？
Now, the only trouble is, what does that prove?
好像是没什么意义，不过却很有趣
Nothing, really. But it's interesting.
第二…后来我看到黄人走出来
Number two.
I saw the Yellow Man come out
跟一个提着公事包的衣冠楚楚的家伙碰头
and meet a well-dressed man carrying an alligator briefcase.
然后他们去了城里
They went to a factory, stood on a staircase and looked into the distance.
走上楼梯，进了那屋
注意听着
Now get this. In the distance, there was a murder.
接着那里就发生了凶杀案
有个毒贩被射杀
A drug dealer was shot to death and a woman had her legs broken.
还有个女人也断了腿
Jeffrey...
杰弗里…
有两个人告诉我
Then two guys told me the police would find drugs in the dead dealer's place.
警方在死掉的毒贩住处找到大量毒品
真不敢相信，你找到了这些
I can't believe what you're finding out.
你还打算继续下去吗？
Are you gonna continue with this?
对
Yeah.
那要到何时才停手？
Until when? What are you gonna do with this?
关于这些情报你打算怎么处理？　　不知道
Well, I don't know.
你还要去她公寓？
You're not going back to her apartment?
对
Yeah.
杰弗里，为什么？
Jeffrey, why?
我发现了些被掩盖很久的事
I'm seeing something that was always hidden.
那是宗很神秘的案件
I'm involved in a mystery. I'm in the middle of a mystery.
我已经神不知鬼不觉的
涉身于其中了
And it's all secret.
你那么喜欢那种神秘感？
You like mysteries that much?
对
Yeah.
你就很神秘
You're a mystery.
我喜欢你
I like you...
很喜欢
very much.
是吗？
Yeah?
杰弗里…别这样
Jeffrey, don't. Please.
你真的担心我吗？
You worry about me? Really?
是的
Yeah.
很惊讶吗？
Is that so surprising?
我非常担心你
Yeah, I worry... a lot.
是我把你扯进来的
I got you into this.
Blue velvet
Whoa- Whoa
She wore blue velvet
Bluer than velvet was the night
Whoa- Whoa- Whoa
Softer than satin was the light
From the stars
She wore blue velvet
Whoa- Whoa
Bluer than velvet were her eyes
Whoa- Whoa- Whoa
Warmer than May her tender sighs
Love was ours
去卧室
Come to my bedroom.
你想要做什么？
What do you want to do?
我正在做呢
I'm doing it.
你是个坏小子吗？
Are you a bad boy?
什么意思？
What do you mean?
想要做坏事吗？
Do you wanna do bad things?
什么都可以
Anything.
你想要怎么样的？
What do you want?
我想你打我
I want you to hurt me.
不！我不想伤害你
No. I don't wanna hurt you. I told you, I wanna help you.
我说过我只想帮你
Dorothy, I know some of what's happening.
桃乐茜，我知道是怎么回事
弗兰克是不是抓了你丈夫和孩子？
Frank has your husband and son, doesn't he?
你得要想办法报警
Dorothy, you gotta do something, go to the police or...
不要报警！
No police!
唐尼，来打我
Don!
- Hit me! - No! No!
不！不！
Get away! Get away from my bed! Stay away!
滚开！从我床上滚下去！
滚开！
你在我身上留下记号了
I have your disease in me now.
他总是让我很开心
It used to make me laugh.
对不起，桃乐茜
I'm sorry, Dorothy.
我得走了
- I should go. - Yes.
是的
你认为我不正常是吗？
You think I'm crazy, don't you?
我想要你留下
I want you to stay.
别恨我
- Don't hate me. - I sure don't hate you.
我当然不会恨你
我没疯
I'm not crazy.
我还能分辨对错
I know the difference between right and wrong.
那很好
That's good.
你是我特别的朋友
You're my special friend.
我把你放在我心里
I still have you inside of me.
那让我振作
It helps me.
我需要你
I need you.
我会给你电话
I'll call you.
好的
OK.
很快就给我打？
Soon?
你不骗我？
- Are you lying to me? - No.
真的？
- Are you sure? - Hey!
你好，宝贝
Hello, baby.
这杂种是谁？
- Who is this fuck? - A friend. He's from the neighbourhood.
是个朋友
就住在附近
只是过来陪我说说话
We were just talking.
你就住在附近
You're from the neighbourhood.
对
Yeah.
那你就是邻居了
You're a neighbour.
你叫什么？好邻居
- Well, what's your name, neighbour? - Jeffrey.
杰弗里
He's a good kid, Frank.
他是个好孩子，弗兰克
给老子闭嘴！
Shut the fuck up!
要我带你兜风吗？
Hey, you wanna go for a ride?
不用，谢了
No, thanks.
不用，谢了？这算是什么意思？
"No, thanks"? What does that mean?
我不想去
- I don't wanna go. - Go where?
去哪儿？兜风
- For a ride. - A ride. Hell, that's a good idea.
兜风！这注意不错
我们走
OK. Let's go.
带上你的外套
Let's go. Get your fuckin' robe!
雷蒙德！
Raymond?
我们去兜兜风
Come on. We're gonna go for a joyride.
兜风
Joyride.
你想要去哪儿？
All right, where do you wanna go?
我明白了
Oh, I know. We got to go to Ben's, right?
我们去看看本如何？
Oh, right. We've got to see Ben.
是的，我们得去看看本
对，我们就去那里
Yeah, we got to, got to, got to, got to.
我们也许全会被杀
We may all be killed.
他真是个娘娘腔，弗兰克
- He's a pussy, Frank. - Yeah, but he's our pussy.
不过他是我们的娘娘腔
- Right, tits? - Pussy heaven.
娘娘腔的天堂
你去过娘娘腔天堂没有？
You ever been to pussy heaven?
没有
No.
他说什么？
- What'd he say? - No. No. Hasn't been to pussy heaven.
不，没去过娘娘腔天堂
警方来点
- Po-lice call. Po-lice call. - Bury that fuck!
好极了
This...
is...
it.
雷蒙德
Raymond?
谢谢
Thank you, Raymond.
弗兰克来了
Frank's here.
过来
Come on. I want you to meet a friend of mine.
我想你来见见我朋友
雷蒙德，去买些啤酒来，记得买上本那份
Hey, Raymond? You get enough beer for Ben, too.
你喜欢什么牌子的啤酒？
- What beer do you like? - Heineken.
喜力
Heineken? Fuck that shit!
什么烂酒！喝蓝带的！
Pabst Blue Ribbon!
带了些朋友过来，还带了些啤酒
I brought some friends, I brought some beer.
好，弗兰克
Fine, Frank, fine.
弗兰克，真是惊喜
Oh, Frank. This is a fine surprise that you brought your friends.
你带了那么多朋友
I love surprises.
我喜欢惊喜
请坐下
Please, sit down.
装腔作势…
Suave... Goddamn, you're one suave fucker.
你真他妈够蠢的！
要来点啤酒吗？
- You want some beer? - Of course, Frank.
当然，弗兰克
Darling.
亲爱的，拿些杯子来
Darling, could you bring some glasses? And we'll have a beer with Frank.
我们和弗兰克喝点小酒
谢谢
Thank you.
请坐下
Please, sit down.
别那么恶心好吗？
Shit, man. How the shit are ya?
好的，弗兰克，最近如何？
Fine, Frank, fine. How are you?
好的不得了
Fuckin' good. I'm real fuckin' good.
真他妈好的不得了
糖色小精灵
今天还活着
Here today,
明天就归西
gone tomorrow.
那话可吓不了我
That doesn't scare me.
我叫保罗，你叫什么？
I'm Paul. What's your name?
杰弗里
Jeffrey.
杯子都在哪儿？
Where's the glasses? That beer's gonna get warm.
啤酒都快热了
我最他妈受不了…就是喝热啤酒！
One thing I can't fuckin' stand is warm beer! It makes me fuckin' puke!
那味道让我要呕吐！
亲爱的，杯子怎么还不拿来？
Darling, where's the glasses?
等等，弗兰克，马上就拿来
Here, Frank. Here come the glasses.
看，来了
See, here are the glasses.
雷蒙德，他妈啤酒都在哪儿？
Raymond, where's the fuckin' beer, man?
就在这儿，弗兰克
It's right here, Frank.
要我倒吗？
- D'you want me to pour it? - No, I want you to fuck it!
不是，我要你拿这干自己！
Shit, yes, pour the fuckin' beer!
当然要你倒了！快给老子满上！
谢谢
Thank you.
来干杯吧
- Let's drink up. - Here's to your health.
这是为你建康而干
Shit, let's drink to somethin' else.
还是找别的理由祝酒吧
让我们为操得愉快而干杯
Let's drink to fucking.
还是说“祝你操得愉快，弗兰克”
Yeah, say "Here's to your fuck, Frank."
随你喜欢，弗兰克
If you like, Frank.
祝你操得愉快
Here's to your fuck. Cheers.
干杯
干杯，真够会装的！
Cheers. Wow. Suave, man.
你真他妈够文雅的！
You are so fuckin' suave.
我们爱本
- Hey, we love Ben. - We love Ben.
- Here's to Ben! - Here's to Ben.
为了本干杯！
嘿，邻居
为了本干杯
Here's to Ben.
- Here's to Ben. - Be polite!
要尊敬些！
为了本干杯
Here's to Ben.
看到没有，本？
See that, Ben?
只要我喜欢，我能叫他做任何事
I can make him do anything I please.
谢谢你敬我酒
Thank you for the toast. That was very nice, neighbour.
真是太谢谢了，邻居
他伤到你的小脸了吗？
Did he hurt your little face?
这样感觉好些了吧？
That feel better?
弗兰克，我给你搞了些东西
Frank, I have something for ya.
抱歉让大家等一下
Would you excuse us for a moment, please?
我喜欢抱歉
Excuse us, por favor.
雷蒙德，你好好看着她
Raymond, do a little baby-sitting.
我是保罗
I'm Paul.
高登要在大白天找他
Gordon went right up to 'em in broad daylight, cos he's the man, right?
反正他是老大
He took those drugs away and it was fuckin' beautiful.
然后就把那些毒品全吞了，真他妈漂亮！
叫糖色小精灵的睡眠精灵
A candy-coloured clown they call the Sandman.
给我了！
让那女人去看她孩子
Let Tits see her kid, huh?
叫糖色小精灵的睡眠精灵
A candy-coloured clown they call the Sandman.
唐尼！唐尼！
Donny! Donny!
唐尼！
Oh, Donny!
不！不！
No! No! Donny, Mama loves you!
唐尼，妈妈爱你
那糖色小精灵
A candy-coloured clown they call the Sandman
他们称它为睡眠精灵
每晚悄悄进入我房间
Tiptoes to my room every night
撒下星尘飒飒私语
Just to sprinkle stardust and to whisper
伴我入眠
"Go to sleep"
万物如此安祥
"Everything is all right"
我闭上双眼
I close my eyes
将自己漂进一个魔法的夜晚
Then I drift away
Into the magic night
我柔柔的道出
I softly say
一个无声的祈祷
A silent prayer
就似那梦想家
Like dreamers do
然后安枕入眠
Then I fall asleep to dream
去那有你的梦乡
My dreams of you
在梦中，我与你相伴而行
In dreams I walk
With you
在梦中，我向你倾诉衷肠
In dreams I talk
To you
在梦中，你属于我
In dreams you're mine
永远永远
All the time
我们在一起…
We're together
好了！
All right! Let's hit the fuckin' road!
我们出去晃晃！
带我们的好邻居去兜兜风！
We're givin' our neighbour a joyride! Let's get on with it!
我们走吧！
Bye, Ben.
再见了，本
Anyone wanna go on a joyride with us?
有谁要和我们一起去兜风吗？
你想要去吗？
How about you? Huh?
你摆张臭脸给谁看？
No smile for Frank? No?
不愿意笑？
去死吧！我们走！
OK, fuck it! Let's go!
想跟雷蒙德一起走吗？来吧
You wanna go with Raymond? Come on.
星期二见，弗兰克
I'll see ya Tuesday, Frank.
好的，本
Right, Ben.
现在天黑了
Now it's dark.
我们来搞吧！
Let's fuck!
我要搞死一切会动的东西！
I'll fuck anything that moves!
我们要去哪儿，弗兰克？
Where are we going, Frank?
带你的好邻居去乡下！
I'm takin' your neighbour out to the fuckin' country.
你喜欢走路吗？
Hey, do you like to walk?
在和你说话呢，混蛋！
- Hey, I'm talkin' to you, shithead. - What?
什么？
He said "What?", Frank.
他说“什么”，弗兰克
什么？
What.
这家伙和你有什么关系？
Hey! What has this fuck got to do with anything?
他妈的！
Jesus, goddamn.
你这该死的家伙！
You fuck!
你在看什么？
What're you looking at?
什么也没看
Nothing.
不许看着我，杂种！
Don't you look at me, fuck!
要让我再见到你看着我，老子杀了你
I shoot when I see the whites of the eyes.
你很像我
You're like me.
看看那里
Oh, look at those.
这些是什么？
What are these?
弗兰克，求求你，我们走吧
- Please, Frank, let's go. - Don't say please, fuckhead!
不许求我！
宝宝想要捏捏它们
Ooh, baby... Ooh, baby wants to pinch them.
怎么了？
What's the matter? Give 'em back. They're just a little red, that's all.
不，把它们还我
怎么了？
它们只是有点红
Ooh, let me feel 'em. Come here.
让我摸摸！来嘛！
放开她！
Leave her alone!
混蛋！
Goddamn!
你给我滚下车来！
Next!
You, out of the car, fuck! Get him out of the car, Raymond!
把他给我带下车，雷蒙德！
弗兰克！弗兰克，他不是故意的！
- Frank! Frank! He didn't mean anything! - Shut up! Shut up.
闭嘴！闭嘴！
真漂亮，真漂亮
Pretty, pretty. Pretty, pretty.
弗兰克，放开他！
Frank, leave him alone!
Frank! Frank!
保罗…
Paul... candy-coloured clown.
“糖色小精灵”
你运气好，还能活着
You're fuckin' lucky to be alive.
A candy-coloured clown they call the Sandman
-  Tiptoes to my room every night - Look at me.
看着我
Just to sprinkle stardust and to whisper
-  "Go to sleep, everything is all right" - Candy-coloured clown.
糖色小精灵
I close my eyes
Then I drift away
别和她走的太近
Don't be a good neighbour to her.
我从我心坎里…
I'll send you a love letter.
向你寄出情书，杂种！
Straight from my heart, fucker!
你明白什么是情书吗？
Do you know what a love letter is?
就是从他妈枪里出来的子弹！
It's a bullet from a fuckin' gun, fucker.
等你收到我的情书
You receive a love letter from me, you are fucked for ever!
你他妈就此完蛋了！
明白吗，杂种？
You understand, fuck?
我会送你下地狱，杂种！
- I'll send you straight to hell, fucker! -  In dreams
I walk
-  With you - In dreams...
在梦中…
我与你同行
- I walk with you. -  In dreams
-  I talk to you - In dreams... I talk... to you.
在梦中，我向你倾诉
-  In dreams you're mine - In dreams... you're mine.
在梦中，你属于我
-  All the time - All...
We're together
-  In dreams, in dreams - For ever in dreams.
永远在梦中
But just
Before the dawn
-  I awake and find - Feel this.
感觉真好
You gone
I can't help it
If I cry
看看我的肌肉
Feel my muscles. Huh?
来看看！
Feel 'em! Huh? You like that?
你喜欢吗？
把他给我抓紧了
Hold him tight for me.
弗兰克，住手！
Frank, stop it!
弗兰克，住手！弗兰克！不要！
Frank, stop it! Frank! Stop!
住手！住手！
Frank, stop it! Stop it!
住手，弗兰克！
Stop it, Frank!
In dreams you're mine
（ 牧场路 ）
打我！
Hit me.
不，唐尼！妈妈爱你！
No, Donny, Mama loves you!
杰弗里，你说的是什么意思？
What do you mean, you're lucky to be able to call me?
什么叫能打电话给我…算是幸运？
Things got out of hand.
事情有些出乎意料
我找到些情报，可能会帮上你父亲
I know some things. They could help your father, but you might get into trouble.
不过也会给你带来麻烦
别管我，你还是和他说吧
Look, forget me. You've got to tell him.
OK. I promise I won't mention you.
我保证不会提到你的
杰弗里，我不开玩笑
Jeffrey, I mean it. It doesn't matter.
不用管我
若没变故那就周五见
- Good. I'll see you Friday, if not before. - OK.
好，再见，桑蒂
- Bye-bye, Sandy. - Bye.
别问我，我不想说
I don't wanna talk about it.
什么都过去了
Everything is OK now. I just don't wanna talk about it.
我不想再提起了
Sometimes it's good to talk things over. For instance, they say many marriages...
有时候还是把事情说出来好，杰弗里
比如说，有很多婚姻
Aunt Barbara... I love you but you're gonna get it.
芭芭拉姨妈
我爱你，不过你不会明白的
高登
Gordon.
高登要在大白天去找他
Gordon went right up to 'em in broad daylight, cos he's the man, right?
反正他是老大
He took those drugs away and it was beautiful.
他把那些毒品全吞了！真是漂亮！
我来！
I got it.
杰弗里，进来吧
- Jeffrey. Come on in. - Jeffrey.
你好，桑蒂
- Hi, Sandy. - Hi, Jeffrey.
你好，杰弗里
- Sorry to bother you, but I need to talk. - OK. Looks like you had a bad face-lift.
很抱歉打搅你，但有些事情必须要说
你的脸怎么破相了
对
- Yeah. - Come on into my study.
去我的书房说
我来给你看些照片
I have to show you some photos and tell you some things about them.
还要告诉你关于他们的事
首先是这张照片
This is the first picture.
是弗兰克布斯
It's Frank Booth.
他是个极端危险的变态人物
He is a very sick and dangerous man.
他的住址就在照片背面
His address is on the back of the photo.
这张是弗兰克和另外一个人
This photo is of Frank and another man as they went into Frank's building.
他们走进弗兰克的住处时拍的
接着是那人出来找第三个人
And then that man came out and met with a third man. This well-dressed guy.
是个衣冠楚楚的家伙
Here's that photo.
这里是那张照片
我好知道有个叫桃乐茜华伦的女人…
I think a woman named Dorothy Vallens is in trouble with these people.
也被卷入了这桩案子
我想是弗兰克绑架了她的丈夫和儿子
I think Frank kidnapped her husband and son. I have no hard proof of this.
不过我没有什么有力证据
桑蒂有参与吗？
- Is Sandy part of this? - Oh, no. No.
没有
还有谁知道你有这些照片？
Who else knows you have these photos?
只有你和冲印照片的人
Just you and the photo lab.
你已经插手管这案子？
- And you're through with this now? - Yes, sir, I am.
是的，先生
可现在你最好快退出
For now, all right, you better be. And Sandy better not be involved with this.
最好桑蒂也与此无关
我只能这么说
准备近期来局里做祥细的口供
Be prepared to come in for further interrogation on this later.
是的，先生
Yes, sir.
没事吧？
- Is everything OK? - Yeah. Is Friday still on?
对，星期五的约会还去吗？
你没把我也供出去？
- You didn't tell him about me? - No.
没有
Why did I ever get you going on this, Jeffrey?
我真不该把你牵涉进这事，杰弗里
星期五的约会当然会去
- Of course Friday's still on. - Great. See ya then.
太好了，那到时见
晚安，威廉斯探长
Good night, Detective Williams.
晚安，桑蒂
- Night, Sandy. - Good night, Jeffrey.
晚安，杰弗里
爸…
Dad?
出什么事了？
What's wrong?
最好是没出什么事
There better be nothin' wrong.
让我看看
我去开　　　谢谢
- I'll get it. - OK, thanks.
晚上好，杰弗里，进来吧
- Jeffrey, come on in. - Thanks, Mrs Williams.
谢谢，威廉斯太太　　　她正在等你
- She's all ready. - OK.
你真漂亮
- You look great. - Thanks.
谢谢
你好，威廉斯探长
- Hello, Detective Williams. - Hello, Jeffrey.
你好，杰弗里
- You all set? - Almost.
好了吗？就快了
约翰，我们得快点了
Hey, John, get a move on.
稍等会，汤姆
Just a minute, Tom.
放轻松点，杰弗里
Easy does it, Jeffrey.
注意自己的举动
Behave yourself. Don't blow it.
别把事情搞杂了
快点，约翰，上车了，伙计
Come on, John. Get it in gear, pal.
再见，杰弗里
So long, Jeffrey. You two have a nice time tonight, OK?
祝你们今晚玩的开心
怎么了？
- OK. - What's goin' on?
只不过是父辈的忠告
Just a little fatherly advice.
没错，杰弗里
That's right, Jeffrey.
来吧
Come on.
再见，爸爸，晚安，妈妈
Bye, Dad.
- Good night, Mom. - Bye. Have a good time.
再见，玩的开心
晚安，桑蒂　　　晚安，汤姆
- Night, Sandy. - Good night, Tom.
杰弗里，刚才是怎么了？
- Jeffrey, what was that all about? - It's nothing.
真的没什么
Really.
能见到你真好
It's good to see you.
我也是
你今晚真漂亮
You look beautiful.
谢谢
Thank you.
Hi.
稍等会
都招呼好了
- It's all taken care of. - OK.
要喝点什么吗？
You want a drink?
想要跳舞吗？
Wanna dance?
Yeah.
Sometimes a wind blows
And you and I
Float
In love
And kiss for ever
In a darkness
And the mysteries of love
我爱你，杰弗里
I love you, Jeffrey.
Come clear
我也爱你
I love you, too.
In you
In me
And show
That we
Are love
再见
Bye. See you later.
那是什么了？
- What's goin' on? - What is it?
什么？
他想要撞我们
They're gonna hit us.
天！这是怎么了？
- Oh, my God, what's wrong? - It's Frank.
那是弗兰克
快滚开！
Move it!
坐稳了！
Hang on.
我甩不掉这家伙
I can't outrun this guy. My father's got a gun at home.
父亲在家里留了把枪
- Jeffrey, no. - Sandy, this guy's a killer. I promise you.
杰弗里，别这样！
桑蒂，这家伙杀人不眨眼，我向你保证
那是麦克！杰弗里，是麦克！
It's Mike! Jeffrey, it's Mike. Oh, my God.
我的天
截下他了，麦克
快从车里滚出来
Get outta the car! Come on! Get outta there!
出来！滚出来！
居然敢和我抢女人，杂种
You stole my girl, you bastard. I'm gonna kick your ass.
该好好给你点颜色瞧瞧
Right here, in front of your own stupid house. Get outta here!
就在你自己家门口给你点教训
快出来！
Mike, stop it.
麦克，住手！
Shut up! Just shut up, all right? Nobody's talkin' to you.
闭嘴！闭会嘴，好吗？
没人和你说话
来吧
Come on, Mike. Look, I don't wanna cause any problems.
我还不想惹麻烦
那是谁？是你老妈吗？
- Who's that? Is that your mother? - Dorothy.
桃乐茜！
- No, come here, you lvy League shit. - She's hurt, in case you didn't notice.
给我过来，你这陀屎
放开我！
Dorothy Vallens?
桃乐茜华伦？
来吧
Come on.
我真的…我很抱歉
I'm really... Hey, I'm sorry.
我很抱歉，我不知道
I'm really sorry. I didn't know. I'm really sorry.
没关系
- It's OK. It's OK. - I thought you were gonna kill him, man.
我还以为你会杀了他
我们得带她离开这里
We've gotta get her outta here.
带她去我家
Go to my house. My father can get an ambulance fast.
我父亲很快就能找来救护车
- His partner won't be there, will he? - Probably not. Why?
他的拍档该不会在吧？
很难说，怎么？
- Nothing. - Watch out for Mike.
没什么
小心麦克
天
Oh, God.
是你吗，杰弗里？
Is that you, Jeffrey?
对，是我
Yeah. It's me.
Oh, Jeffrey...
Jeffrey...
爸！妈！
Dad? Mom?
我在这儿，宝贝
- I'm in here, honey. - Mom!
好了，马上就来
All right, I'll be right there.
爸爸在家吗？
- Is Dad home? - No. He oughta...
不在，他走…
你得快叫救护车来
You better call him. And... get an ambulance.
你们这是去哪儿了？
Where have you been?
天
Oh, God.
天，他们伤了你
Oh, God, they've hurt him. Oh, Jeffrey! Jeffrey, Jeffrey, hold me!
杰弗里！抱着我！没事了
- Hold me! Hold me! - It's OK, it's OK.
抱着我！天！
我的神秘情人
My secret lover.
我已经叫了救护车
I've called for an ambulance. The police are on their way.
警察也马上就会到
Don't get the police!
不要报警！
不要！
Stop it!
我爱你！你要爱我！
I love you! Love me!
他在我身上留下了记号
He put his disease in me.
告诉我不会有事
Tell me it's all right I opened myself to you.
我把自己都交给你了
告诉我不会有事
- Tell me it's all right. - Sandy, please...
桑蒂…
- Sandy? - I'll get a coat to put on her.
我去给她拿件外套来
杰弗里，这是怎么了？
Jeffrey? What's going on here?
我会和你解释的
I'll tell you.
他们…他们把他的头伤得好重
They... they've hurt his head.
是谁，桃乐茜？
Who, Dorothy?
唐尼.救救他
Don. Help him.
救救他
Help him.
答应我你会去救他！
Promise me you'll help him!
他在我身上做了记号
He put his disease in me.
你要和我们一起坐救护车走
Would you like to come in the ambulance?
还是开自己车？
I'll be right with you.
我随后就来
我得走了
I should go.
那就快走
- Go. - Sandy...
抱着我！
Hold me! I'm falling!
我要掉下去了！我要掉下去了！
I'm falling! Hold me!
你对我撒谎
- You lied to me. - Sandy, please, forgive me.
桑蒂，求求你，原谅我
我爱你
I love you.
我原谅你，杰弗里
I forgive you, Jeffrey.
我爱你
I love you.
天，我爱你
我…
I... But I couldn't watch that.
但我看不下去
她没事吧？
- Is she OK? - Yeah, she's OK.
对，没事
Get your father. Tell him to send the police to Dorothy's apartment.
尽快找到你父亲
让她派手下去桃乐茜的公寓
要他尽快，现在我得挂了
Tell him to hurry. I'm leaving right now.
杰弗里，不要
- Jeffrey, no. - I have to.
我必须得走了
- I love you. - Oh, God, be careful.
我爱你
天，你要保重
I will, believe me.
会的，相信我
Where...
我的梦又算是什么？
Where is my dream?
这是紧急事件
Look, this is an emergency.
他说有人受伤了
He said someone was hurt and he wants Detective Williams there.
他想要威廉斯探长能在场
我们也不知道…这时候他在哪里
We do not know his whereabouts at this time.
那就去找他！
Well, find him!
快退后趴下
Get back and stay down.
这是弗兰克布斯住的26号公寓
He's going to apartment 26.
警官，我们现在在弗兰克地方了
Lieutenant, we're at Frank's place now. The raid has commenced, as scheduled.
按原计划进行
原地待命
Stay in place.
Love letters straight from your heart
25号是空屋，可以从那里走
Number 25 is vacant, so maybe we can go through there.
Keep us so near
While apart
I'm not alone
In the night
就让他们自己来找你吧
I'm gonna let them find you on their own.
When I can have
All the love
You write
I memorise
Every line
老天
威廉斯警官！
Detective Williams.
- Detective Williams? - Williams here. Is that you, Jeffrey?
这是威廉斯探长，是你吗，杰弗里？
对，我藏在桃乐茜华伦的住所
Yeah, it's me. I'm hiding in Dorothy Vallens' apartment.
弗兰克化妆成那个衣冠楚楚的家伙上来了
Frank is on his way in a well-dressed-man disguise. I've got no way out...
我现在无路可退…
他有无线电
He's got a radio.
Jeffrey!
威廉斯探长？
Detective Williams? I'm hiding in the back bedroom.
我就藏在卧室里，请尽快赶到
Please hurry.
嗨，好邻居
Hey, neighbour. You shit-for-brains, man! You forgot I have a police radio!
你真是蠢货！
你居然忘了…我有警方的无线电
这个衣冠楚楚的家伙
One well-dressed fuckin' man knows where your fuckin' cute little butt's hidin'.
知道你那可爱的小屁股藏在哪儿
你这个蠢杂种
Stupid fuck.
想跟我玩！
Fuck with me, man.
我进来了
Here I come, ready or not.
准备好没有
按计划进行
混蛋！
You fuck!
我听的到你说的话，蠢货！
I can hear your fuckin' radio, you stupid shit!
你活不久了，伙计
You got about one fuckin' second to live, buddy!
你会觉得抱歉的，先生
You're one sorry piece of shit, mister.
真漂亮，真漂亮！
Hey, pretty, pretty!
他妈的！你躲到哪儿去了？
What the fuck... Where are you? Where are you?
你在哪儿？
Oh, Jeffrey.
都结束了，杰弗里
It's all over, Jeffrey.
And kiss for ever
In a darkness
And the mysteries of love
Come clear
And dance
In light
In you
杰弗里，午餐准备好了
- Jeffrey, lunch is ready. - OK.
In me
And show
That we...
你们这是在干什么？
- How you guys doin'? - Hey, Jeffrey.
- Hey, Jeff. Feelin' much better now, Jeff. - Good deal, Dad.
我感觉好多了，杰弗
是的，爸爸
桑蒂，你看
Sandy, look.
午餐时间
Lunchtime.
好的，杰弗里　　　听起来不错
- OK, Jeffrey. - Sounds good.
快过来看看这个
Jeffrey, come over here and look at this.
看！
Look.
我在外面见过他
Yeah, I saw him outside.
也许知更鸟都来了
Maybe the robins are here.
我不明白…它们是怎么办到的
I don't see how they could do that. I could never eat a bug.
换了我，是怎么也吞不下虫子的
这世界无奇不有，对吗？
It's a strange world.
Isn't it?
Sometimes a wind blows
And the mysteries of love
Come clear
而我依然可见
And I still can see
蓝丝绒
Blue velvet
透过我的眼泪
Through
My
Tears
CHD极品 ☆☆☆☆☆☆☆☆ ZSK字幕